# 陈飞阳

# 178-0111-4068 | chenfeiyang@bjfu.edu.cn Haidian District, Beijing



#### PERSONAL SUMMARY

- Second year of undergraduate of computer science and technology major (innovative experimental class) of Beijing Forestry University is reading, and he already has certain project development experience.
- Presided over a national college student innovation training project. "Based on CNN and LSTM text sentiment classification algorithm research.
- Has managed a summer social practice group for 19 people. Using the summer vacation for 30 days, he learned from zero
  and eventually developed the "Kailin Beilin" micro-letter app. The results were formally launched on 2017-8-15, and it was
  practically convenient. Newly-introduced campus life at the time of admission, with a total of more than 10,000 visits, was
  incorporated into the sixth National University Student Science and Technology Innovation Works and Patent Achievement
  Exhibition Promotion Fair.
- Instructed by the Cui Xiaohui teacher of this institute to independently develop the "level assessment service system for soil
  and water conservation monitoring units of production and construction projects", and is currently applying for computer
  software copyrights, which is currently in the state of acceptance.
- Successed as a director of the Planning Department of the Federation of Student Associations of the Association of Schools
  and Schools and the Planning Department of the Employment Service Center of the School. He is good at copywriting and
  editing. He is currently the Minister of the Ministry of Information of the Employment Service Center and has organized mock
  job hunting competitions and career planning competitions., Job Salons and other activities, good at collecting information
  and scientific analysis of the data; also served as a long-term squad leader, has organized many collective activities, good
  communication and coordination, with excellent leadership.

### **EDUCATIONAL EXPERIENCE**

**Beijing Forestry University** 

Sep 2016 - Jun 2020

Bachelor Computer Science & Discourse (Innovation Lab) Information Academy

Beijing

- GPA: 3.54 / 4.0 (pre-professional 2%) (Teacher Year)
- GPA: 3.56 / 4.0 (in his freshman year and sophomore last year, he is currently reading in sophomore year)

Changsha First High School

Sep 2013 - Jun 2016

Changsha City

## **HONORS & AWARDS**

- Mathematical Contest In Modeling Honorable Mention (2018)
- Excellent student officer (2016-2017)
- Top Scholarship for Excellent Students (2016-2017)

### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Water and Soil Conservation Monitoring Unit Level Evaluation Service System for Production and Construction Projects May 2018 - Sep 2019

developers Beijing

< UI>

- With the introduction of the "digital + economic" Internet + "government policy of the new era" and the use of information and communication technologies and Internet platforms, the deep integration of the Internet and traditional industries and the creation of a new development ecology have become an inevitable trend. This represents a new social form that fully utilizes the optimization and integration of the Internet in the allocation of social resources, integrates the Internet's innovation results deeply into the economic and social fields, and enhances the innovation and productivity of the entire society. More extensive new forms of economic development based on the Internet as the infrastructure and implementation tools.
- To this end, based on the "Department of Soil and Water Conservation Society of China," the service innovation requirements of the monitoring unit level evaluation business, I designed this system, aiming at the public evaluation

process of the level of monitoring units, to society, universities, research Other agencies provide "one-stop" services.

• At present, this system is applying for a software copyright patent and passed the preliminary examination.

# A text sentiment analysis algorithm based on CNN and LSTM

May 2018 - Sep 2019

Host

Beijing

• This project will improve the existing algorithms from two aspects of the new emotion word vector learning framework and the structure of the improved neural network and propose new algorithms to improve its accuracy in multi-category sentiment analysis. At present, this project is still in progress. The expected results will mainly include: publishing a SCI or EI search paper; a text sentiment analysis website embedding a new algorithm of the neural network model demo.

### SOCIETY AND ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

#### **Employment Affairs Center**

Jun 2017 -

Minister Information Department

Beijing

- In the first year of my freshman year, I worked as a director of the Planning Department of the Copywriting Planning Department and the School's Employment Affairs Center of the school's social organization. I participated in numerous large-scale campus activities such as the Guinness Cross Country Championships, Spiritual Night, and Green. In the second year of school, he served as director of the Information Department of the Center for Employment Affairs of the Institute and organized activities such as simulated job contests, career planning contests, and employment salons. He took practical actions to participate in the construction of schools and colleges, and made developments for schools and colleges. Actively contribute, actively practice the core values of the society, obey the law, be noble in moral character, be upright, and have won the second class of "The Analects of Confucius" at the Beijing Forestry University "Outstanding Student"honorary title;
- Long-time squad leader, organized several class activities, actively mobilized classmates to participate in various class advanced activities, and made full use of the new media platform. Each classmate sent exclusive birthday wishes, the class was cohesive and won the Beijing Municipality. The fifth most solidarity class contest competition, the fifth prize, good style class and other awards;
- Actively participated in voluntary service activities. He went to the Yuhua Disability Center in Chaoyang District, Beijing to serve as a volunteer to help handicapped adolescents, and also served as a volunteer on the first youth television publicity lesson "Open Talk" broadcast on CCTV1. Audience guests; Actively participate in social practice activities, and lead the team to use the summer vacation time to independently develop the "Bei Lin" micro-letter program, which effectively facilitates the new campus student's campus life at the time of entry. The result is the second prize for the student's response to the summer school. Social practice "advanced personal" honorary title.

#### SKILLS/CERTIFICATES AND OTHER

- SKILLS: Python, C++, R
- WINNING EXPERIENCE: 2018 Mathematical Contest In Modeling Honorable Mention, 9th National College Student
  Mathematics Contest, Third Prize Thirty-eighth Beijing University Students Mathematical Contest Third Prize, Third Prize of
  the 9th Lanqiao Cup Provincial Class, First-class Scholarship for Outstanding Students, Grade Three Excellent Student of the
  School, Excellent Student Cadre at the School Level, and Advanced Summer School Social Practice Personal
- ACTIVITIES: Beijing's third most Unite class competition competition fifth, Beijing Forestry University summer social practice
  achievements answer second prize, I on the North Forest WeChat public account (operation), ITOintheuniversalcenter
  WeChat public account (operation)